

NODAR JMUKHADZE

IT DIRECTOR



Contacts

- ♣ Date of Birth 12.06.1992
- ◆ Tbilisi, Gamrekeli street
- ⚠ Nodo.itspec@gmail.com
- 995 551 499 333

Key Skills

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Project Management Hardware engineer Network designer Telecommunications Helpdesk Process Web design Graphic design Backup & Recovery OS system-level software

IT Skills

IT Policy

Microsoft Office Suit

IT Troubleshooting

Html

PHP CSS

Photoshop

Illustrator

Adobe ID

PBX

Firewall

Virtualization VmWare

Windows

Linux OS

CCTV

Access system

Cloud NAS

Filmora

Soft Skills

Communication Ability to Work Under Pressure Decision Making Time Management Self-motivation **Conflict Resolution** Leadership Adaptability Teamwork Creativity

Professional Summary

Experienced IT professional with a history in all different areas of information technology. Master of computer science and operation from over a 6+ of working with and on computers. Developed communication, cooperation, and leadership skills from IT support career. Knowledge candidate ready to utilize 7+ years of experience in IT to excel in any

Work Experience

IT Director - New Vision University/Hospital

June 2019 - Till today

Responsibilities:

- Oversee all technology operations (e.g. network security) and evaluate them according to established goals
- Analyze the business requirements of all departments to determine their technology needs
- Purchase efficient and cost effective technological equipment and software
- Coordinate IT technician and supervise computer scientists, technicians and other professionals to provide guidance
- Assist in building relationships with vendors and creating cost-efficient contracts
- Maintains quality service by enforcing quality and customer service standards; analyzing and resolving quality and customer service problems; identifying trends; recommending system improvements.
- Devise and establish IT policies and systems to support the implementation of strategies set by upper management-Review IT network information to gain insight into areas of potential improvement.

IT Manager - Innovato Corp

Dec 2017 - April 2019

Responsibilities:

- Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.
- Review IT network information to gain insight into areas of potential improvement.
- Understand current and future business goals and ongoing IT issues to ensure business succes
- Develop innovative network troubleshooting methods that reduce downtime and lower repair costs
- Responsible for creating and administering disaster plans that will keep the company functional in the event of a crisis.
- Maintains quality service by enforcing quality and customer service standards; analyzing and resolving quality and

IT Project Manager - NextBrand Marketing

Sep 2015 - Dec 2017

Responsibilities:

- Supervise and direct IT personnel
- Develop a detailed project plan to monitor and track progress
- Establish and maintain relationships with third parties/vendors
- Test, evaluate, and make decisions about new technology for the business.
- Ensure that all projects are delivered on-time, within scope and within budget.
- Integrate information technologies into the company for optimal effectivenes.
- Participate in business-wide meetings to provide insight into technical requirements.
- Delegate project tasks based on junior staff members' individual strengths, skill sets and experience levels.

IT Support - Ultimatus Services

Feb 2014 - Sep 2015

Responsibilities:

- Testing new technology
- Setting up accounts for new users
- Repairing and replacing equipment as necessary

Languages

- Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks
- Responding in a timely manner to service issues and requests
- Providing technical support across the company (this may be in person , over the phone or Ticket system)

Interests

6 Music

Movies



Drawing





Education

Local school in Tyumen Russia Tbilisi. First experimental school Tbilisi. Georgian Technical University 1998-2000 2001-2010

2010-2013